I cannot create images directly with this chat, however, U.com has other options, right?
So let me come back to new chat. And this time, I want to create an image using this very tool
that we're in. So I come here and say, "Today, I want to U-2..." Okay, let me also click on "Create
Mode." I want you to generate me an image of, let's say, for example, a cat running to catch a dog
and the dog is running away. So I want the image to be as real as possible to carry the comedy
and communicate the joke, right? And my create mode is on as well. So I also copy this one and
send my command to see what I will get, right? And it's thinking it's developing a plan and it's
generating image as you see. So it is also able to do that as well.
Yes, so as you see, the image is generated and if I wait a little bit more, yes,
my image is now available, right? So as you see, this cat is running after this dog and it's
very mad at him. So yes, this is what we got, right? So we can open this image up, we can download it,
we can share it with whoever that we want. And as easy as that, you know, just like any other chat
box that is available out there, u.com is also useful, right?